https://www.shepherdshillacademy.org/privacy-policy/

Current Project
Shepherd's Hill Academy responds to Covid-19.
PRIVACY POLICY
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you fill out the Contact Us form.
When completing the Contact US form, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number. When completing the Donation information, you may be asked for your credit card through the secure PayPal, Authorize.net or another secured Third-Party site.  You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
Shepherd’s Hill Academy may use third-party vendors, including Google, to show ads or information for Shepherd’s Hill Academy across the internet. Through the use of cookies, third-party vendors are able to serve more relevant ads based on past visits to our website.  Visitors to shepherdshillacademy.org are free to opt-out of Google’s use of cookies at any time by visiting Google’s Ads Settings. Visitors can also opt-out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
To send periodic emails.  The email address you provide on the Contact Us form will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your individual needs.
If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related service information, etc.
Note:  If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How do we protect your information?
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway provider’s (Pay Pal, Authorize.net) database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.  After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We, therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We, therefore, will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act); we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products, and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Description of your situation (message on Contact Us form)
The description of your situation, or any message, that you leave on our Contact Us form is strictly only submitted to the necessary Staff of SHA to assess your individual needs.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Social Media Terms and Conditions
Review our full terms and conditions for commenting and engaging with Shepherd’s Hill Academy online on our Digital Media Communications Page.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.  This policy was last modified on November 26, 2019.
Contact Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
Shepherd’s Hill Academy
2200 Price Rd,
Martin, Georgia 30557
office@shepherdshillacademy.org
(706) 779-5766
2200 Price Road
Martin,
2020 © Shepherd's Hill Academy / All Rights Reserved. Accreditation/Affiliation / Created by MWI
